Welcome to Asimgit, please subscribe to my channel. I like my video. In this video, we will learn how to
apply the Flask app on Python Anywhere. After you log into your account on Python Anywhere,
then you can go to the web.
And here you can click on Add New Web App. And this will be the domain or URL for your
web application. And then click on Next. And here you can select Python Web Framework. We are going
to go with the Flask and the Python version. I will select Python 3.10. And then you can see
Quick Start New Flask project. This file is your startup file or your Flask project.
And we just going to leave this name as it is. And then click on Next.
And now we can see all done. Your web app is now set up. And here is when you scroll down a bit,
you can see the source code pack 12 file. And this is our directory where our source code
is for our web application. And this is how we're working directory. And we can go to this
on my site from here. Or we can go back or here and click on Files.
And under my site, you can see Flask app. And you can click on it.
And this is the default code for our Flask app. And you can also run from here your application.
And now our application is starting. And now we can test our web application and under
the web. This is the URL of my web application. I'm just going to click on this one.
And we get this message hello from Flask, which is the code over here. So this way you can
apply the Flask page application on Python anywhere. To keep on learning, please subscribe to
my channel Asyncube. Like my video, give support to me, and thank you for watching.